So the big one is here.
So many flies?
Look, this corpse is quite fresh.
Looks like it just died.
Are you illiterate?
Is that how you define "fresh"?
It's weird.
Fast Gun.
If this thing reanimates,
snap that hostage's
head off.
Otherwise,
you'll die with me.
It's a person.
Master, you're still alive?
Are we...
Kill me.
Kill me!
Come on.
It wouldn't be right
to kill you the first time we meet.
I'll get you out of here, huh?
Fast Gun!
Snap his head off!
Snap it off!
Not again!
I told you to snap his head off,
but you didn't.
Useless.
Buddy,
what's your name?
Why are you down here?
[Crew ID]
[Name: Song Cai]
You are Song Cai?
Did you spread the Twilight Grass?
Was it you?
No?
Then who brought
the Twilight Grass to Nan'an
and started spreading it?
What do you mean?
The culprit is
the one who brought
this Evil God's ancestral shrine aboard?
How could such a big ancestral shrine
be brought aboard?
Was it a group of soldiers?
Well, let me ask you.
Is the "NP" you carved on the bed
related to the culprit?
Pi...
Seriously.
Another one swearing? Calling me a pig?
You're lucky.
Let's go! Let's go!
Who are you two?
Zhang Ruipu is dying,
and you're asking who I am?
Song Cai?
So we've met before.
You were Zhang Ruipu's subordinate.
Pi...
He was trying to say pitcher plant.
What does it have to do with the culprit?
How did you follow us out?
Forget it.
Let's leave here first.
[Traitor]
Stop right there!
Easy, easy.
[Zhang Hailou]
I need to see Miss Dong.
I have important matters to report.
You can say what you wanna say right here.
Miss Dong.
There was a disturbance
on the ship just now.
We have already checked it.
Initial assessment shows that
the disturbance came from
the bottom of the hold.
We found
a very strange place there.
We are trying to get inside to check.
[Zhang Hailou]
Zhang Hailou,
what on earth are you doing?
Will you find what I want?
Or...
are you the traitor?
[Zhang Hailou]
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 6]
[Countdown: 28 hours]
You're awake?
I thought
you were going to die on my ship.
Here, have some water.
Luckily my wife
knows a little about medicine.
When the ship docks,
you need to get off.
I don't want to get into any trouble.
Buddy.
How long have I been out?
You slept for a whole night.
See? It's already dawn.
Are we still in Balongzhou?
Yes.
I'm delivering goods along the way,
and I'll turn back soon.
I remember your ship
will return to
Balongzhou Pier around 4:00 PM.
Drop me off there.
I have things to do.
How do you know that so clearly?
Buddy,
I know the engine on your ship
isn't working well.
I'll fix it for you.
But can you get me
a ticket for the Nan'an?
Just consider it doing me a small favor.
You know my engine isn't working well?
Can you really fix it?
I can.
It's a deal then.
Buddy,
you're injured this badly.
What do you need to do?
What's more important than your life?
I have to get on the Nan'an
before it sets sail.
Those who spread the toxic weed
are very dangerous.
Zhang Hailou, you must be careful.
Good morning, the fastest gun
in the South Seas.
I've already fixed your nose.
You're welcome.
[Bottom hold of Nan'an]
This tea is really good.
What...
did you do to my room?
We made a major breakthrough
entering the ancestral shrine this time.
[Bottom hold of Nan'an]
Of course, there are also many doubts.
For instance, who
got this ancestral shrine onto the ship?
Such a big scene.
Did Miss Dong know about it?
If she did, how did it get on?
Did the captain know?
How was it declared at customs?
Also,
when we were in the ancestral shrine,
we saw many signs of a fight.
Who left them?
There were also many bullet marks on it.
Don't you know guns best?
What kind of gun was it?
I don't know.
I don't remember!
You have to know.
You have to remember.
Was the gun a Luger?
This is very important.
Oh, right.
After you fell down that tunnel,
what did you see?
Try to think back.
You know that, right?
The tunnel where you could see
many, many versions of yourself.
The one that made you cry out of fear.
Mom!
Think hard,
Fast Gun.
We've fallen into a big scheme.
[Bottom hold of Nan'an]
This is a big scheme.
What big scheme?
You're behind all this!
Black magic.
It's all black magic.
You are the root of all evil.
If I get rid of you,
everything will be over.
It's one thing
if you can't solve the problem.
But you can't try to eliminate
the person who raised it,
right?
The only thing we know now is that
the people who spread the Twilight Grass
[The one who spread the Twilight Grass]
[The Evil God's ancestral shrine]
[Ten years ago]
and those who brought
the Evil God's ancestral shrine on board
are the same group,
[Bottom hold of Nan'an]
which is the group from Panhua Reef.
But what exactly is their goal?
Why did they spread the Twilight Grass?
And why did they bring
this ancestral shrine on board?
What's the connection
between these 2 things?
There's no time.
Shrimpie,
what would you do if you were me?
When you encounter something
in the future,
you must stay calm.
Never act on impulse.
But I have no time.
Think more about
how it will affect the people around you.
Mr. Steven,
do you have faith?
[Dukun]
Very good.
You're giving me a
western magic vibe right now.
What are you trying to do?
I don't believe in these things.
You don't need to believe.
Just do as I say.
Someone else will.
I don't understand.
Will this draw the robbers out?
Yes.
By then, when you see me,
just start reciting the scripture.
The hour is coming!
When you see me,
just start reciting the scripture.
We must face misfortune!
That's all.
Don't worry.
If you can't remember it,
just look in the mirror.
I wrote the scripture on your face.
Zhang!
Hang in there, bro.
Hold on for one more day,
and you can kill me.
You fixed the ship for me.
It's worth more than a ticket.
Here is your payment.
Well, I wish you success
with your business.
Thank you.
This smell...
It's so familiar.
The smell of cured meat.
Why is it here?
Burn all the evidence.
Don't let anyone go!
That adjutant?
Why is he here?
Hello. I want to get on the ship.
Can you expedite it for me?
[Xiacheng Minghua Shipping Company]
[Countdown: 16 hours]
Hello,
I'm looking for someone.
His name is Zhang Hailou.
He wears gold-rimmed glasses.
I'm his brother.
We got separated.
One moment.
Sorry, sir.
We don't have a guest here
under the name Zhang Hailou.
He has another name,
Zhang Ruipu.
[359: Zhang Hailian]
[345: Zhang Ruipu]
I'll wait for him here.
If you see him,
please let him know.
Okay.
The food here is this good?
Good afternoon.
You look really handsome today, buddy.
Who is this?
Hi.
Is that the Miracle Doctor of Balai?
I heard people like him
are born with special abilities.
Yeah.
He does look different from normal people.
Are you okay?
He...
He's poisoned!
Yes, he is!
[Dukun]
I heard
a lot of people in Balai got poisoned
by this stuff.
This poison can be fatal.
Everyone, stay away from him!
Step back!
-Help me...
-Stay away!
Doctor,
save me!
Calm down!
Save me!
Pull yourself together!
There's one day to go.
Recite the scripture!
The hour is coming!
We must face misfortune!
Only the children who believe in God
will be blessed.
O Lord Almighty!
Please bless us and help this poor man!
Oh! Bless us!
The wound hasn't healed after so long.
Zhang Hailou,
where are you?
I can't smell you.
Hailou?
What happened over there?
I heard someone was poisoned
by that deadly grass poison,
and a doctor is trying to save him
right on the spot.
I'm cured?
I'm cured!
That's amazing.
Thank you, doctor!
Thank you!
Miracle Doctor of Balai!
-Thank you, Miracle Doctor of Balai!
-Miracle Doctor of Balai!
This idiot.
What is he up to?
In the future, if you have any illnesses,
just come to Steven.
Steven can solve them all for you.
Got it?
Come on, a round of applause!
He's a messenger sent by heaven
to help us!
Steven! Steven!
So what does that mean, Adjutant?
Strange.
Such a strong smell of cured meat,
how come no one else smells it?
Is it just me?
Miracle Doctor! Miracle Doctor!
Miracle Doctor!
None of this is right.
I'll draw them away first
to protect Hailou.
This is an illness
that taking Chinese medicine
and having surgery cannot solve.
But here today,
we witnessed a miracle!
This is a miracle!
It really is poison.
Stay awake.
Think of something.
The smell of cured meat?
He's dead?
It's not a human-skin mask.
It really is that adjutant.
Where am I?
Where is Chen Xifeng?
Why can't I move?
This guy spits razor blades.
We can't keep him under control.
How about we kill him?
That guy in the wheelchair is smart.
Let's give him a chance
and make him work for us.
Too bad he can't walk.
Let's just kill him.
Then let's
ask the great god
to swap their legs,
so the smart one can stand.
Shrimpie.
Zhang Haixia.
I was just in the wheelchair.
Zhang Hailou.
It's fine. I won't die.
I'll take you out first.
What's wrong?
I can't feel my legs.
These are...
My legs...
I can feel my legs now.
They got swapped.
Shrimpie.
You can stand up now.
Impossible.
How can there be a way
to swap legs in this world?
Something must be wrong.
Let's get out first.
Come on.
Come.
Leave me behind.
I can't burden you and Mentor.
Nonsense.
I will definitely get you out.
You know this feeling best, right?
I can never walk again.
And I can never go on missions again.
I'm just a burden, right?
You're not a burden.
Look.
Now that you're in trouble,
I can't help at all.
I only drag you down.
Put me down.
Stop messing around!
You'll die here.
Then let me die.
If I become a burden to you,
I...
I'd rather die.
You're my brother.
Stay alive for me.
I can't
live like this.
Kill me.
Help me.
I shouldn't live like this.
You know this feeling best, right?
And I can never go on missions again.
You are just a burden.
You shouldn't even be alive.
You will drag everyone down,
including your mentor and Zhang Hailou.
Do it, Zhang Haixia.
He was poisoned
by the Twilight Grass Poison,
yet he has managed to hold on for so long.